UTU New York State Legislative Director Files 5711
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Unsafe Working Conditions, Buffalo, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 70)
- Unsafe Working Conditions, Alfred E. Perlman Freight Yard, Selkirk, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  September 29, 1976
- Hazardous Conditions, Bridge 89, Roseton, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  October 10, 1976
- Unsafe Working Conditions on ConRail West Shore Branch, Kingston, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  November 26, 1976
- Derail at West Haverstraw, Bulletin to Put Service into Operation, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  October 13, 1976
- Delaware and Hudson General Committee Modification Operating Rule 99, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 75)
- Public Service Commission: Correspondence Regarding Rule 99 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  Found empty October 7, 2014. No date.
- Complaint of General Chairman Miller, Bush Terminal: Unsafe Conditions, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 77)
- Delaware and Hudson Railroad Case 24843, Trains 34 and 35, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  July 15, 1968
- Delaware and Hudson Trains 9 and 10, 34 and 35, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  August 2, 1968
- Brooklyn Eastern District Railroad: Dangerous and Hazardous Conditions, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  October 23, 1968
- Bison Yard: Unsafe Tracks 24, 29, 45, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 81)
- Niagara Junction Railroad, Niagara Falls, New York: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 82)
- South Buffalo Railroad, Unsafe Conditions on Railroad Cars, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  April 7, 1969
- Delaware and Hudson Oneonta, New York: Unsafe Conditions, Low Joints, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  June 12, 1969
- Boston and Maine Railroad, Mechanicsville, New York: Unsafe Conditions, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 85)
- Delaware and Hudson Caboose, Whitehall, New York: Unsafe, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  October 13, 1969
- Norfolk and Western Railroad: Unsafe Conditions, Buffalo, New York, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  June 11, 1970
- Delaware and Hudson Railroad: Caboose and Unsafe Conditions, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  August 17, 1970
- Buffalo Creek Railroad: Unsafe Working Conditions, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  October 23, 1970
- Department of Environmental Conservatism: Regarding Unhealthy Idling of Buses, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  February 18, 1971
- Handling of Cabooses at Whitehall, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  July 16, 1971
- Unsafe Conditions, Buffalo, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  August 24, 1971
- Vegetation growth in Buffalo Area, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 93)
- Boston and Maine Railroad: Unsafe Conditions at Rotterdam Yard, Rotterdam, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  September 1971
- Mechanicsville, New York, Removal of Wreck Crane, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  November 19, 1971
- South Buffalo Railway, Unsafe Conditions at Lackawanna, New York, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  June 6, 1972
- Sayre, Pennsylvania, Weeds and Debris, Sayre Pennsylvania to Manchester New York, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  August 22, 1972
- Delaware and Hudson: Mohawk Yard, Schenectady, New York - Request for derail to be installed, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 98)
  October 18, 1972
- Freight Trains Operated Without Caboose on Rear, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 99)
- Bus Standee Violations, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 100)
  November 6, 1972
- Boston and Maine: Mobile Crane Operating on Main Track between Hoosick Junction, New York and Eagle Bridge, New York, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 101)
- South Buffalo Railway 1585, All Test on Cinder Ladies, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 102)
  June 10, 1975
- Boston and Maine: 470 - Unsafe Working Conditions in the Boston and Maine Yard, Mechanicsville, New York, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 103)
  August 29, 1975
- Unsafe Working Conditions, Oneonta, New York, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 104)
- Hazardous Condition in Walkway between Main Track 1 and 2 on the Creek Bridge, Batavia, New York, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 105)
- Maiden Lane Crossing (Public Service Commission), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 106)
- Miscellaneous Department of Transportation Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 107)
- Railroad Safety Act (United States Congress), 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 108)
- Rubber Air Hoses "Stiff", 1974 (Box 20, Folder 109)
- Boston and Maine: Penn-Central - Violation of Power Brake Law of 1958, Rotterdam Junction, New York, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 110)
- Amended Operating Rules (b) and E, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 111)
- Miscellaneous Locomotive Complaints, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 112)
  1972, 1976
- Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 113)
- Albany Port Authority, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 114)
- Staten Island Rapid Transit Company, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 115)
- Horus of Service Violations, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 116)
- Local 1582 Audit and New York State Matter, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 117)
- Institute Manned Baggage Service on Adirondack Operating between New York City and Montreal, Canada, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  September 26, 1975
- Hydrocyanic Acid Poison Gas within Train BMX-1, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 119)
- Health Hazards - J.E. Kraus, Junior, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 120)
- Poughkeepsie Bridge, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 121)
  December 3, 1975
- Purchasing of Uniforms by Railroad Operating Employees, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 122)
  April 9, 1976